Guide to the Thomas Raynesford Lounsbury Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, Series I
  - Kinney, John C., 1881 (Box 11, Folder 260)
  - Kitchel, Corneliua Ladd, 1897-1898 (Box 11, Folder 260)
  - Kittredge, George Lyman, 1893-1900 (Box 11, Folder 260)
  - Kline, William, 1898 (Box 11, Folder 260)
  - Knabenshue, S. S., 1909 (Box 11, Folder 261)
  - Knapp, Mrs. Adeline R., 1892-1894 (Box 11, Folder 261)
  - Knapp, H., 1883 (Box 11, Folder 261)
  - Knapp, William Ireland, 1906 (Box 11, Folder 261)
  - Knickerbocker, George S., 1878 (Box 11, Folder 262)
  - Knight, Albert H., 1896 (Box 11, Folder 262)
  - Knight, William Lowick, 1912 (Box 11, Folder 262)
  - Knortz, Karl, 1886-1890 (Box 11, Folder 262)
  - Knox, Charles R., 1910 (Box 11, Folder 262)
  - Knudsen, Lydia, 1912 (Box 11, Folder 262)
  - Koch, Theodore W., 1900-1903 (Box 11, Folder 263)
  - Koenig, Jacob Adolph, 1886-1899 (Box 11, Folder 263)
  - Kountze, Herman, 1891 (Box 11, Folder 263)
  - Kramer, A. Walter, 1913 (Box 11, Folder 263)
  - Kullman, P. C., 1896 (Box 11, Folder 263)
  - Kwong Ki Chiu, 1880-1881 (Box 11, Folder 263)
  - L - General (Box 12, Folder 264)
  - Lakin, L. K., 1913 (Box 12, Folder 265)
  - Lamar, A. M., 1878 (Box 12, Folder 265)
  - Lamberton, John P., 1907 (Box 12, Folder 265)
  - Lane, Edgar H., 1902 (Box 12, Folder 265)
  - Lane, John, 1909 (Box 12, Folder 265)
  - Lane, Martha A. L., 1910 (Box 12, Folder 265)
  - Lane, Sarah, 1878 (Box 12, Folder 265)
  - Lang, Alice Derby, undated (Box 12, Folder 266)
  - Lang, Andrew, 1896 (Box 12, Folder 266)
  - Langton, Alice C., 1910-1911 (Box 12, Folder 266)
  - Lanier, Sidney, 1880 (Box 12, Folder 266)
  - Lanman, Charles R., 1874-1915 (Box 12, Folder 266)
  - Larimore, J. H., 1909 (Box 12, Folder 266)
  - Latham, Adelaide J., undated (Box 12, Folder 267)
  - Latham, Harry L., 1893 (Box 12, Folder 267)
  - Lathrop, George Parsons, 1883-1894 (Box 12, Folder 267)
  - Laubenthal, John, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 267)
  - Law, James T., 1887 (Box 12, Folder 267)
  - Law, Walter W., 1892-1893 (Box 12, Folder 267)
  - Lawler, Harry A., 1890 (Box 12, Folder 268)
  - Lawton, Frederick, 1908 (Box 12, Folder 268)
  - Lawton, William C., 1898 (Box 12, Folder 268)
  - Learned, Emily C., 1911 (Box 12, Folder 268)
  - Learned, H. Barrett, 1907-1915 (Box 12, Folder 268)
  - Learned, J. E., 1892-1894 (Box 12, Folder 268)
  - Leary, Cathie M., 1899 (Box 12, Folder 269)
  - Leath, W., 1884 (Box 12, Folder 269)
  - Lecky, James, 1882 (Box 12, Folder 269)
  - Lee, Henry, 1891 (Box 12, Folder 269)
  - Lee, James Melvin, 1915 (Box 12, Folder 269)
  - Lee, Sir Sidney(*), 1902-1914 (Box 12, Folder 270)
  - Lefferts, Marshall, 1906 (Box 12, Folder 270)
  - Legler, Thomas A., 1889 (Box 12, Folder 270)
  - Leighton, R. F., 1880 (Box 12, Folder 271)
  - Le Mesurier, Mrs. Lilian Bruce, 1892-1909 (Box 12, Folder 271)
  - Lentilhon, Eugene, 1890 (Box 12, Folder 271)
  - Leonard, Elizabeth, 1902 (Box 12, Folder 271)
  - Lerch, Charles A., 1892-1894 (Box 12, Folder 271)
  - Lewis, Alonzo Norton, 1872-1887 (Box 12, Folder 272)
  - Lewis, C. W., 1901-1912 (Box 12, Folder 272)
  - Lewis, Charlton Miner, 1896-1911 (Box 12, Folder 272)
  - Lewis, Charlton Thomas, 1891-1892 (Box 12, Folder 272)
  - Lewis, Dudley Payne, 1902 (Box 12, Folder 272)
  - Libby, O. G., 1895 (Box 12, Folder 273)
  - Liebschutz, N., 1913 (Box 12, Folder 273)
  - Lincoln, L. J. B., 1894-1895 (Box 12, Folder 273)
  - Lindsay, Lady Blanche, undated (Box 12, Folder 273)
  - Lindsley, E. Purdy, 1887 (Box 12, Folder 273)
  - Lines, Edwin S., 1896 (Box 12, Folder 273)
  - Lipsey, Robert G., 1911 (Box 12, Folder 274)
  - Literary Digest
    See: John Bower, box 2, folder 42
  - Little, Robbins, 1884 (Box 12, Folder 274)
  - Llano, A., 1911 (Box 12, Folder 274)
  - Lloyd, W. S., 1913 (Box 12, Folder 274)
  - Lloyd, William J., 1883 (Box 12, Folder 274)
  - Lobo, M. F., 1904 (Box 12, Folder 275)
  - Lockhart, R. C., 1876 (Box 12, Folder 275)
  - Lockwood, Edwin H., 1906 (Box 12, Folder 275)
  - Lockwood, Sara (Mrs. William E.), 1887-1889 (Box 12, Folder 275)
  - Lodge, Henry Cabot(*), 1879-1911 (Box 12, Folder 276)
  - Loeb, Rowena, 1896 (Box 12, Folder 277)
  - Long, Frank L., 1913 (Box 12, Folder 277)
  - Long, John D., 1910 (Box 12, Folder 277)
  - Longwell, Sue A., 1879 (Box 12, Folder 277)
  - Lord, W. W., 1882 (Box 12, Folder 277)
  - Lorenz, C. K., 1881 (Box 12, Folder 277)
  - Lorillard, Louis L., 1892 (Box 12, Folder 277)
  - Lounsberry, C. C., 1895 (Box 12, Folder 277)
  - Lounsberry, John W., 1880 (Box 12, Folder 277)
  - Lounsberry, N.A., 1879 (Box 12, Folder 277)
  - Lounsberry, Edward, 1892 (Box 12, Folder 277)
  - Lounsbury, Henrietta, 1892 (Box 12, Folder 277)
  - Lounsbury, Henry(*), 1872-1894 (Box 12, Folder 278-279)
  - Lounsbury, Jennie Dungan (Folwell)(*), 1861-1869 (Box 12, Folder 280-283)
  - Lounsbury, Jennie Dungan (Folwell)(*), 1870-1905, undated (Box 13, Folder 284-293)
  - Lounsbury, Phineas, 1886-1889 (Box 13, Folder 294)
  - Lounsbury, Thomas, 1859, undated (Box 13, Folder 294)
  - Lounsbury, Walter W.(*), 1884-1900 (Box 13, Folder 295)
  - Lovett, A. Sidney, Jr., 1912 (Box 14, Folder 296)
  - Lowe, Walter I., 1894 (Box 14, Folder 296)
  - Lowell, A. Lawrence, 1904-1909 (Box 14, Folder 296)
  - Lowell, James Russell, 1870-1876 (Box 14, Folder 296)
  - Lowes, John Livingstone, 1905 (Box 14, Folder 297)
  - Ludlow, Helen W., 1879 (Box 14, Folder 297)
  - Luquiens, Frederick Bliss, 1913 (Box 14, Folder 297)
  - Lusk, Graham, undated (Box 14, Folder 297)
  - Luther, F. S., 1913 (Box 14, Folder 297)
  - Luty, James, 1913 (Box 14, Folder 297)
  - Lydenberg, H. M., 1913 (Box 14, Folder 298)
  - Lyman, Delia
    See: Delia Lyman Porter, box 17, folder 368
  - Lynch, Daniel, 1912 (Box 14, Folder 298)
  - Lyon, L., 1882 (Box 14, Folder 298)
  - Lyon, William L., 1883 (Box 14, Folder 298)
  - M - General (Box 14, Folder 299)
  - Mabie, Hamilton Wright, 1889-1906 (Box 14, Folder 300)
  - McAndrew, W. A., 1895 (Box 14, Folder 300)
  - McCabe, Edward R. W., 1914 (Box 14, Folder 300)
  - McCabe, Jeanie (Mrs. W. G.), 1897 (Box 14, Folder 300)
  - McCabe, W. Gordon(*), 1896-1915 (Box 14, Folder 301)
  - Macallum, Archibald B., 1912 (Box 14, Folder 302)
  - McClelland, J., 1894 (Box 14, Folder 302)
  - McClelland, W. C., 1885 (Box 14, Folder 302)
  - McClumpha, Charles F., 1890-1893 (Box 14, Folder 302)
  - McClurg, Alexander C., 1898 (Box 14, Folder 302)
  - McCollum, James L., 1912 (Box 14, Folder 302)
  - McCord, Charles C., 1912 (Box 14, Folder 302)
  - McCormick, William S., 1897 (Box 14, Folder 302)
  - MacCoun, Townsend, 1884 (Box 14, Folder 303)
  - McCracken, D. G., 1909 (Box 14, Folder 303)
  - MacCracken, Henry M., 1915 (Box 14, Folder 303)
  - McCullagh, John Henry, 1893 (Box 14, Folder 303)
  - McDaniels, J. H., 1911 (Box 14, Folder 303)
  - McDavid, Millie (Mrs. Ned), 1909 (Box 14, Folder 303)
  - MacDonnell, Alexander, 1876 (Box 14, Folder 303)
  - McElroy, J. G. R., 1887-1889 (Box 14, Folder 303)
  - McElroy, William, 1913 (Box 14, Folder 303)
  - MacGrath, Claire, 1898 (Box 14, Folder 303)
  - McIntire, Albert W., 1895-1896 (Box 14, Folder 303)
  - Mackall, Leonard L., 1900 (Box 14, Folder 304)
  - Mackay, Elizabeth Cary, 1905-1908 (Box 14, Folder 304)
  - Mackay, Mary, 1879-1882 (Box 14, Folder 304)
  - MacKaye, Percy, 1909 (Box 14, Folder 304)
  - McKeever, J. Laurence, 1891 (Box 14, Folder 304)
  - McKelway, St. Claire, 1903 (Box 14, Folder 304)
  - McKibbin, Gilbert H., 1899 (Box 14, Folder 304)
  - McKinney, Mary Stuart, 1898-1901 (Box 14, Folder 304)
  - Mackintosh, Frank S., 1909 (Box 14, Folder 304)
  - McLaughlin, Margaret, 1904 (Box 14, Folder 304)
  - McLaughlin, Sarah B., 1894-1915 (Box 14, Folder 305)
  - McLaughlin, Tompkins, 1890 (Box 14, Folder 305)
  - MacLean, Mary E.(*), 1904-1915 (Box 14, Folder 305)
  - McMath, F. M., 1894 (Box 14, Folder 306)
  - Macmillan & Co.(*), 1874-1898 (Box 14, Folder 306)
    See: George P. Brett, box 2, folder 44
  - MacMurray, A. A., 1878 (Box 14, Folder 306)
  - McNeil, Jennie(*), 1862-1863 (Box 14, Folder 307-308)
  - McSweeney, John, 1911 (Box 14, Folder 309)
  - Madden, Edwin, 1907 (Box 14, Folder 309)
  - Mahony, John Dennis, 1906 (Box 14, Folder 309)
  - Malley, Edward, 1893 (Box 14, Folder 309)
  - Mallory, Herbert S., 1909 (Box 14, Folder 309)
  - Malone, John, 1904 (Box 14, Folder 309)
  - Malone, Walter, 1909 (Box 14, Folder 309)
  - Mangam, Daniel D., Jr., 1884 (Box 14, Folder 309)
  - Manly, John Matthews, 1894 (Box 14, Folder 309)
  - Mann, James, 1882 (Box 14, Folder 310)
  - Mann, Matthew D., 1897 (Box 14, Folder 310)
  - Mansfield, Burton, 1909 (Box 14, Folder 310)
  - Mansfield, Mary A., undated (Box 14, Folder 310)
  - March, Alden, 1912 (Box 14, Folder 310)
  - March, F. A., 1879-1908 (Box 14, Folder 310)
  - March, F. A., Jr., 1896-1897 (Box 14, Folder 310)
  - Mariotti, Eva, 1897 (Box 14, Folder 310)
  - Marsh, Othniel Charles, 1894 (Box 14, Folder 311)
  - Marsh, R. C., 1875 (Box 14, Folder 311)
  - Marston, Moses, 1881 (Box 14, Folder 311)
  - Martin, Alfred B., undated (Box 14, Folder 311)
  - Martin, Edward S., 1912-1913 (Box 14, Folder 311)
  - Martin, James G., undated (Box 14, Folder 311)
  - Marty, Jemuel Gates, 1894 (Box 14, Folder 311)
  - Marvin, Arthur, 1895 (Box 14, Folder 311)
  - Marvin, Earle R., 1895 (Box 14, Folder 311)
  - Marvin, Edwin E., 1887 (Box 14, Folder 311)
  - Mason, Edward T., 1895 (Box 14, Folder 312)
  - Mason, Francis O.(*), 1871-1882 (Box 14, Folder 312)
  - Mason, George Webb, 1878 (Box 14, Folder 313)
  - Mather, Frank Jewett, Jr., 1896 (Box 14, Folder 313)
  - Mathews, Florence, 1892 (Box 14, Folder 313)
  - Mathews, Harold C., 1892 (Box 14, Folder 313)
  - Matthews, Albert, 1892-1913 (Box 14, Folder 313)
  - Matthews, James Brander(*), 1888-1914 (Box 15, Folder 314-315)
  - May, L. R., 1877 (Box 15, Folder 316)
  - Mead, C. M., 1907 (Box 15, Folder 316)
  - Mead, R. F., 1911 (Box 15, Folder 316)
  - Means, Katharine Gower (Mrs. W. F.), 1912 (Box 15, Folder 316)
  - Means, Stewart, 1910 (Box 15, Folder 316)
  - Medlicott, M., undated (Box 15, Folder 316)
  - Medlicott, William Gibbons(*), 1872-1882 (Box 15, Folder 317)
  - Meeker, Arthur, 1902 (Box 15, Folder 318)
  - Meeker, J. Edward, 1912 (Box 15, Folder 318)
  - Meigs, Ferris Jacob, 1889 (Box 15, Folder 318)
  - Melson, K., 1892 (Box 15, Folder 318)
  - Menner, Robert J., 1907 (Box 15, Folder 318)
  - Mensch, Morris H., 1909 (Box 15, Folder 318)
  - Mercer, Samuel David, 1891-1895 (Box 15, Folder 318)
  - Merkle, N. Louise, 1905 (Box 15, Folder 318)
  - Merriam, G. & C. Co., 1871-1899 (Box 15, Folder 319)
  - Merrill, W. F., 1910 (Box 15, Folder 319)
  - Merwin, S. E., Jr., 1874 (Box 15, Folder 319)
  - Metcalf, Henry A., 1909 (Box 15, Folder 319)
  - Metcalf, Martha K., 1913 (Box 15, Folder 319)
  - Mew, Egan, 1898 (Box 15, Folder 319)
  - Meyer, Anne N. (Mrs. Alfred), 1885 (Box 15, Folder 319)
  - Milburn, John George, 1896 (Box 15, Folder 320)
  - Miles, Henry C., 1877 (Box 15, Folder 320)
  - Milford, Arthur B., 1892-1894 (Box 15, Folder 320)
  - Miller, C. H., 1905 (Box 15, Folder 320)
  - Miller, Charles Ransom, 1900 (Box 15, Folder 320)
  - Miller, Edgar Calvin Leroy, 1904 (Box 15, Folder 320)
  - Miller, George Douglas, 1913 (Box 15, Folder 320)
  - Miller, Jahu Dewitt, 1895-1901 (Box 15, Folder 320)
  - Miller, Nettie Lounsbury (Mrs. William A.), 1890-1895 (Box 15, Folder 321)
  - Mills, Benjamin F., 1902 (Box 15, Folder 321)
  - Minor, W. C., 1902-1905 (Box 15, Folder 321)
  - Mitchell, Donald Grant(*), 1883-1900, undated (Box 15, Folder 322)
  - Mitchell, Edwin Knox, 1899-1900 (Box 15, Folder 323)
  - Mitchell, S. Weir, 1904-1905 (Box 15, Folder 323)
  - Mixter, William G., 1889-1902 (Box 15, Folder 323)
  - Moak, Nathaniel C., 1882-1886 (Box 15, Folder 324)
  - Monroe, Ebert C., 1890 (Box 15, Folder 324)
  - Montague, William Lewis, 1873-1874 (Box 15, Folder 324)
  - Monteith, John, 1909 (Box 15, Folder 324)
  - Montfort, Maria P., 1878 (Box 15, Folder 324)
  - Montgomery, Henry, 1878 (Box 15, Folder 324)
  - Montgomery, W. J., 1903 (Box 15, Folder 324)
  - Moore, D. Thomas, 1908 (Box 15, Folder 325)
  - Moore, Frank Gardner, 1905 (Box 15, Folder 325)
  - Morfill, W. R., 1894-1899 (Box 15, Folder 325)
  - Morgan, Forrest, 1894-1913 (Box 15, Folder 325)
  - Morgan, Julius S., 1902 (Box 15, Folder 325)
  - Morgan, Morris H., 1904 (Box 15, Folder 325)
  - Morgan, Robert, 1876 (Box 15, Folder 325)
  - Morison, Nathaniel Holmes, 1873 (Box 15, Folder 326)
  - Morley, Frederick H., 1909 (Box 15, Folder 326)
  - Morley, Henry, 1892 (Box 15, Folder 326)
  - Morris, E. P., 1899 (Box 15, Folder 326)
  - Morris, Eugenia L., 1914 (Box 15, Folder 326)
  - Morris, John L., 1883 (Box 15, Folder 326)
  - Morrow, James M. C., 1874 (Box 15, Folder 327)
  - Norse, Mrs. C. S., 1910 (Box 15, Folder 327)
  - Morse, Edward L., 1882 (Box 15, Folder 327)
  - Morse, Edward S.(*), 1908-1914 (Box 15, Folder 327)
  - Morse, Gardner, 1878 (Box 15, Folder 328)
  - Moses, Montrose, 1903 (Box 15, Folder 328)
  - Mott, John M., 1899 (Box 15, Folder 328)
  - Moulton, Charles Wells, 1889-1899 (Box 15, Folder 328)
  - Muckle, Richard, 1882 (Box 15, Folder 328)
  - Muensterberg, Hugo, 1904 (Box 15, Folder 328)
  - Munger, Harriet Osgood (Mrs. Theodore), 1896 (Box 15, Folder 329)
  - Munger, Rose M., 1901 (Box 15, Folder 329)
  - Munger, Theodore T., 1893-1909 (Box 15, Folder 329)
  - Munson, Mrs. E. G., undated (Box 15, Folder 329)
  - Murphy, Frederick, 1896 (Box 15, Folder 329)
  - Murphy, W. Walton, 1883 (Box 15, Folder 329)
  - Murray, George, 1905 (Box 15, Folder 330)
  - Murray, J. A. H., 1896-1902 (Box 15, Folder 330)
  - Murray, Thomas G., 1879 (Box 15, Folder 330)
  - Murrell, Thomas W., 1913 (Box 15, Folder 330)
  - Myers, Harl, 1888-1890 (Box 15, Folder 330)
  - N & O - General (Box 16, Folder 331)
  - Napier, Arthur Sampson, 1898 (Box 16, Folder 332)
  - Napton, H. P., 1904-1913 (Box 16, Folder 332)
  - *Nation (Box 16, Folder 333)
    See: Howard de Wolf Fuller, box 7, folder 61 See: Wendell P. Garrison, box 7, folder 171-172
  - National Institute of Arts and Letters(*), 1900-1914 (Box 16, Folder 334)
    See: Robert Underwood Johnson, box 11, folder 248
  - Neftel, Mrs., 1896 (Box 16, Folder 335)
  - Neil, Roderic M., 1914 (Box 16, Folder 335)
  - Nelson, Cora, 1909 (Box 16, Folder 335)
  - Nelson, Theophilus, 1894 (Box 16, Folder 335)
  - Nesmith, Charlotte, 1886 (Box 16, Folder 335)
  - Nettleton, George Henry, 1909-1914 (Box 16, Folder 335)
  - New England Association of Teachers of English
    See: George H. Browne, box 2, folder 53
  - New York Times
    See: Henry Brougham, box 2, folder 48 See: William Bayard Hale, box 8, folder 196
  - New York Tribune
  - Newberry, John S., 1883 (Box 16, Folder 336)
  - Newberry, Truman H., 1884 (Box 16, Folder 336)
  - Newton, Clifford, undated (Box 16, Folder 336)
  - Newton, Hubert Anson, 1885 (Box 16, Folder 336)
  - Nice, H. W., 1889 (Box 16, Folder 337)
  - Nicholson, D., 1895 (Box 16, Folder 337)
  - Nicholson, Edward W. B., 1894-1899 (Box 16, Folder 337)
  - Nicholson, John Page, 1913 (Box 16, Folder 337)
  - Nicholson, Watson(*), 1904-1911 (Box 16, Folder 337)
  - Nicola, Felix, 1893 (Box 16, Folder 338)
  - Nicola, Oliver P., 1893 (Box 16, Folder 338)
  - Nicolay, Helen, 1913-1914 (Box 16, Folder 338)
  - Niemeyor, John Henry, 1899 (Box 16, Folder 338)
  - Norris, Howes, Jr., 1894 (Box 16, Folder 338)
  - North, Ernest Dressel, 1914 (Box 16, Folder 338)
  - North, S. H. D., 1905 (Box 16, Folder 338)
  - North American Review
    See: John E. Barron, box 1, folder 25 See: G. T. Ferris, box 6, folder 144
  - Northrup., Birdsey Grant, 1879 (Box 16, Folder 339)
  - Northrup, Cyrus, 1878 (Box 16, Folder 339)
  - Northup, Clark S., 1912 (Box 16, Folder 339)
  - Norton, Charles L., 1883 (Box 16, Folder 339)
  - Norton, Grace Fallow, 1887 (Box 16, Folder 339)
  - Norwood, Robert, 1879 (Box 16, Folder 340)
  - Nourse, Edward E., 1893-1894 (Box 16, Folder 340)
  - Noyes, Atherton, 1903 (Box 16, Folder 340)
  - Noyes, Stephen B., 1881 (Box 16, Folder 340)
  - Nystrom, John W., 1883 (Box 16, Folder 340)
  - Oakford, Ellen, undated (Box 16, Folder 341)
  - Oertel, Hanns, 1907-1914 (Box 16, Folder 341)
  - Ogden, Rollo, 1900 (Box 16, Folder 341)
  - Olcott, Marjorie, 1912 (Box 16, Folder 341)
  - Oldroyd, O. H., 1880 (Box 16, Folder 341)
  - Olendorf, John, 1893 (Box 16, Folder 341)
  - Oliver, Fanny M., 1892 (Box 16, Folder 341)
  - Olney, Jeremiah, 1889 (Box 16, Folder 341)
  - Olschki, Leo S., 1893 (Box 16, Folder 341)
  - Olson, A. B., 1909 (Box 16, Folder 341)
  - O'Neal, R. F., 1913 (Box 16, Folder 342)
  - Orcutt, William Dana, 1906-1907 (Box 16, Folder 342)
  - Osborn, Norris G., 1894-1904 (Box 16, Folder 342)
  - Osborne, Arthur S., 1893 (Box 16, Folder 342)
  - Osborne, C. A., 1906 (Box 16, Folder 342)
  - Osborne, Elizabeth A., 1914 (Box 16, Folder 342)
  - Osgood, James R.(*), 1877-1891 (Box 16, Folder 343)
  - Osier, Sir William, 1909-1911 (Box 16, Folder 344)
  - Our Continent
    See: Daniel Brinton, box 2, folder 47
  - Outerbridge, A. E., 1875 (Box 16, Folder 344)
  - Owen, Edward T., 1873-1887 (Box 16, Folder 344)
  - P - General (Box 16, Folder 345)
  - Packard, Lewis R., 1876 (Box 16, Folder 346)
  - Page, Curtis Hidden, 1905-1909 (Box 16, Folder 346)
  - Page, D., 1893 (Box 16, Folder 346)
  - Page, Joan, 1882 (Box 16, Folder 346)
  - Page, Samuel David, 1882-1913 (Box 16, Folder 346)
  - Page, Thomas Nelson(*), 1896-1913 (Box 16, Folder 347)
  - Paine, Willis S., 1911 (Box 16, Folder 348)
  - Palmer, Arthur Hubbell, 1894-1907 (Box 16, Folder 348)
  - Pancoast, Henry Spackman, 1894 (Box 16, Folder 348)
  - Paradise, Scott Hurtt, 1913 (Box 16, Folder 348)
  - Pardee, H. E. G., 1886 (Box 16, Folder 348)
  - Parish, Augustine S., 1880 (Box 16, Folder 348)
  - Parker, Annie F., 1900 (Box 16, Folder 348)
  - Parker, E. A. D., 1883 (Box 16, Folder 348)
  - Parker, Edwin Pond(*), 1899-1908 (Box 16, Folder 349)
  - Parker, Harris, 1906 (Box 16, Folder 349)
  - Parker, Horatio W., 1911 (Box 16, Folder 349)
  - Parker, John Henry, 1878 (Box 16, Folder 349)
  - Parker, William Belmont, 1904-1905 (Box 16, Folder 350)
  - Parker, W. E., 1881 (Box 16, Folder 350)
  - Parkhurst, Lewis, 1888-1894 (Box 16, Folder 350)
  - Parrott, Thomas More, 1904 (Box 16, Folder 350)
  - Paterson, George B.(*), 1895-1903 (Box 16, Folder 351)
  - Pattee, Fred Lewis, 1889 (Box 16, Folder 352)
  - Patten, Frank C., 1895 (Box 16, Folder 352)
  - Patterson, Anna, 1894 (Box 16, Folder 352)
  - Patterson, T. A., 1911 (Box 16, Folder 352)
  - Pattison, C. Harwood, 1879 (Box 16, Folder 352)
  - Pattison, P. K., 1895 (Box 16, Folder 352)
  - Pearce, J. W., 1896 (Box 16, Folder 353)
  - Pearson, J., 1881 (Box 16, Folder 353)
  - Peck, Lilly H., 1894 (Box 16, Folder 353)
  - Peck, Tracy, 1872-1885 (Box 16, Folder 353)
  - Peckham, Frederick A., 1891-1892 (Box 16, Folder 353)
  - Peets, Cyrus Beery, 1905-1907 (Box 16, Folder 354)
  - Pierce, James Mills, 1886-1888 (Box 16, Folder 354)
  - Pellissier, Adeline, 1913 (Box 16, Folder 354)
  - Penfield, Sam Lewis, 1882-1895 (Box 16, Folder 354)
  - Penniman, James H., 1892 (Box 16, Folder 354)
  - Perkins, Mary, 1888 (Box 17, Folder 355)
  - Perrin, Bernadotte, 1896-1906 (Box 17, Folder 355)
  - Perry, Aaron Jenkins, 1909 (Box 17, Folder 355)
  - Perry, Bliss(*), 1896-1908 (Box 17, Folder 356)
  - Perry, George, 1880-1882 (Box 17, Folder 357)
  - Perry, Thomas Sargeant, 1905-1909 (Box 17, Folder 357)
  - Pery, Edmund, 1912 (Box 17, Folder 357)
  - Peters, John E., undated (Box 17, Folder 357)
  - Pettit, James Sumner, 1902-1904 (Box 17, Folder 357)
  - Peyton, John Lewis, 1882-1895 (Box 17, Folder 357)
  - Pfeiffer, Robert E., 1912 (Box 17, Folder 357)
  - Phayne, J. F., 1891 (Box 17, Folder 357)
  - Phelps, Annabel H. (Mrs. W. L.), 1912 (Box 17, Folder 358)
  - Phelps, Charles Edward D., 1905 (Box 17, Folder 358)
  - Phelps, Edward John, 1892 (Box 17, Folder 358)
  - Phelps, Edward Johnson, 1885 (Box 17, Folder 358)
  - Phelps, Mary E., 1895 (Box 17, Folder 358)
  - Phelps, R. H., 1894 (Box 17, Folder 358)
  - Phelps, William Lyon(*), 1892-1915 (Box 17, Folder 359)
  - Phelps, William Walter, 1872-1875 (Box 17, Folder 360)
  - Phillips, Andrew M.(*), 1892-1912 (Box 17, Folder 360)
  - Phillips, Mary E., 1909-1912 (Box 17, Folder 361)
  - Phillips, O. B., 1908 (Box 17, Folder 361)
  - Phinney, Elihu, 1882 (Box 17, Folder 362)
  - Phipps, Annie C. (Mrs. Henry), 1892-1900 (Box 17, Folder 362)
  - Phipps, Henry, Jr.(*), 1892-1908 (Box 17, Folder 362)
  - Phipps, John Schaffer, 1896 (Box 17, Folder 363)
  - Phipson, Evacustes, 1904-1909 (Box 17, Folder 363)
  - Pickett, Mrs. C., 1912 (Box 17, Folder 363)
  - Pierce, Edwin, 1892-1906 (Box 17, Folder 363)
  - Pierce, George Winslow, 1903-1911 (Box 17, Folder 363)
  - Pierce, John, 1889-1890 (Box 17, Folder 364)
  - Pierce, Robert, 1895 (Box 17, Folder 364)
  - Pierson, Charles Wheeler, 1886 (Box 17, Folder 364)
  - Pike, William Henry, 1910 (Box 17, Folder 364)
  - Pillsbury, Mrs. J. H., 1908 (Box 17, Folder 364)
  - Pinkham, George Ripley, 1894 (Box 17, Folder 365)
  - Pinkney, H. H., 1895 (Box 17, Folder 365)
  - Pirsson, Louis V., 1895-1896 (Box 17, Folder 365)
  - Pitkin, Jane, 1913 (Box 17, Folder 365)
  - Pitman, Eizak, 1879-1880 (Box 17, Folder 365)
  - Platner, Samuel Ball, 1897-1913 (Box 17, Folder 366)
  - Platt, Mary Joy, 1878-1890 (Box 17, Folder 366)
  - Platt, Johnson T., 1876-1879 (Box 17, Folder 366)
  - Platt, Washington, 1911 (Box 17, Folder 366)
  - Poland, W. C., 1888-1891 (Box 17, Folder 367)
  - Poole, Reginald Lane, 1885 (Box 17, Folder 367)
  - Poole, William F., 1884-1887 (Box 17, Folder 367)
  - Porter, Charlotte, 1908 (Box 17, Folder 368)
  - Porter, Delia Lyman, 1889, 1894, undated (Box 17, Folder 368)
  - Porter, Eleanor H., 1908 (Box 17, Folder 368)
  - Porter, John Addison, 1886 (Box 17, Folder 368)
  - Porter, Noah, 1859-1888 (Box 17, Folder 368)
  - Potter, Frances Squire, 1905 (Box 17, Folder 369)
  - Potts, William, 1893 (Box 17, Folder 369)
  - Potwin, Lemuel, 1877-1892 (Box 17, Folder 369)
  - Powell, H. Y., 1885-1899 (Box 17, Folder 369)
  - Powell, Joseph, 1881 (Box 17, Folder 369)
  - Powers, William H., 1906 (Box 17, Folder 369)
  - Pratt, Dan T., 1884-1886 (Box 17, Folder 370)
  - Pratt, Robert, 1903 (Box 17, Folder 370)
  - Pratt, Willard, 1875 (Box 17, Folder 370)
  - Preston, Robert L., 1914 (Box 17, Folder 370)
  - Pribul, F., 1892 (Box 17, Folder 370)
  - Price, William, 1887-1905 (Box 17, Folder 370)
  - Prince, Walter F., 1902 (Box 17, Folder 371)
  - Prior, Thomas N., 1896 (Box 17, Folder 371)
  - Pritchett, Henry S., 1909 (Box 17, Folder 371)
  - Probst, George, 1912 (Box 17, Folder 371)
  - Prudden, Henry A., 1873 (Box 17, Folder 371)
  - Prudden, Theophil M., 1895 (Box 17, Folder 371)
  - Pugh, William H., 1896 (Box 17, Folder 372)
  - Purdy, Clara R., 1915 (Box 17, Folder 372)
  - Putnam, George Haven, 1892-1914 (Box 17, Folder 372)
  - Putnam, Herbert, 1904 (Box 17, Folder 372)
  - Quackenbos, John D., 1890 (Box 17, Folder 373)
  - Quantock, Andrew, 1906-1908 (Box 17, Folder 373)
  - Quinby, Charles, 1913 (Box 17, Folder 373)
  - Quincy, Mary, 1909 (Box 17, Folder 373)
  - Quinlan, Agnes Clive, 1913 (Box 17, Folder 373)
  - Quinn, M. Loretto, 1910 (Box 17, Folder 373)
  - Quintard, Frederick H., 1894 (Box 17, Folder 373)
  - R - General (Box 17, Folder 374)
  - Rae, William, 1906-1908 (Box 17, Folder 375)
  - Railey, Mrs. C. L., 1896 (Box 17, Folder 375)
  - Ralph, Julian, 1895 (Box 17, Folder 375)
  - Rand, Avery & Co., 1877-1879 (Box 17, Folder 375)
  - Rankin, Jean Sherwood (Mrs. A. W.), 1902-1915 (Box 18, Folder 376)
  - Rappleye, Harrison, 1880 (Box 18, Folder 376)
  - Rappleye, Peter W., 1874 (Box 18, Folder 376)
  - Raymond, James, 1894 (Box 18, Folder 376)